[
  {
    "prompt": "astar price",
    "response": "0.15366327046522843",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-09 16:45:36.380126"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "create a new key and name it 'test'",
    "response": "Keypair created and stored in file - ./ai_llm/local_keys/test.txt",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 00:44:41.270539"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the balance of Bholu on Aleph Zero Testnet Network?",
    "response": "This is the raw balance of the address - 25301989315289120, please adjust for the decimals",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 01:14:48.641900"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the balance of Bholu on Polkadot?",
    "response": "This is the raw balance of the address - 0, please adjust for the decimals",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 01:20:28.474473"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "delete my keypair titled 'test'",
    "response": "Keypair file deleted - ./ai_llm/local_keys/test.txt",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 01:33:01.658635"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "delete/remove my keypair under the alias vking",
    "response": "Keypair file deleted - ./ai_llm/local_keys/vking.txt",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 01:40:47.339964"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "delete/remove my keypair under the alias Vking",
    "response": "Keypair file deleted - ./ai_llm/local_keys/Vking.txt",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 01:41:16.687064"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "remove address 'Bholu' from the address book",
    "response": "alias Bholu deleted from the address book",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 12:25:25.360834"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "add address '12NUJVQF6AMMBtjSFq2eASunCxQ9SisdNG5ZWb8AVkftuupw' as vking alias",
    "response": "alias 'vking' added for the address - ''12NUJVQF6AMMBtjSFq2eASunCxQ9SisdNG5ZWb8AVkftuupw''",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 12:38:25.278397"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "add address '12NUJVQF6AMMBtjSFq2eASunCxQ9SisdNG5ZWb8AVkftuupw' as vking alias",
    "response": "alias 'vking' added for the address - '12NUJVQF6AMMBtjSFq2eASunCxQ9SisdNG5ZWb8AVkftuupw'",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 12:44:15.373269"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "remove address for vking from the address book",
    "response": "alias vking deleted from the address book",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 12:45:50.482496"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "create a new keypair and name it 'default'",
    "response": "Keypair created and stored in file - ./ai_llm/local_keys/default.txt",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 14:40:03.620414"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "add address '5ECfLuhUtoBVzHVSfCDTpCQrh61NmiC3qMm1Kfic4TNB2nJH' in the address book under the alias Sam",
    "response": "alias 'Sam' added for the address - '5ECfLuhUtoBVzHVSfCDTpCQrh61NmiC3qMm1Kfic4TNB2nJH'",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 14:59:20.881973"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "transfer 10000000000 AZERO to Sam on Aleph Zero network",
    "response": "transfer execution failed due to the error - {'code': 1010, 'message': 'Invalid Transaction', 'data': 'Inability to pay some fees (e.g. account balance too low)'}",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 15:13:48.756602"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "transfer 10000000000 AZERO to Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet network",
    "response": "transfer executed successfully for 10000000000 to Sam using the rpc wss://aleph-zero-testnet-rpc.dwellir.com",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 15:14:47.971461"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "timed transfer - 10000000000 AZERO to Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet network in 5 days",
    "response": "scheduled transfer : 10000000000 to Sam on 2024-03-15 15:55:31.321329 on wss://aleph-zero-testnet-rpc.dwellir.com",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 15:55:32.745026"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "transfer 10000000000 AZERO to Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet network",
    "response": "transfer executed successfully for 10000000000 to Sam using the rpc wss://aleph-zero-testnet-rpc.dwellir.com",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-10 15:59:08.991105"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the price of bitcoin?",
    "response": "72375.905",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11 22:39:02.490087"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the price of ASTR?",
    "response": "0.1653163882123984",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11 22:45:00.273920"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the balance of Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet?",
    "response": "This is the raw balance of the address - 50000000000, please adjust for the decimals",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11 22:57:54.927868"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the price of DOT ?",
    "response": "11.1845",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11 23:57:01.327328"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "transfer 10000000 AZERO to Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet",
    "response": "transfer executed successfully for 10000000 to Sam using the rpc wss://aleph-zero-testnet-rpc.dwellir.com",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11 23:59:45.134331"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the balance of Sam on Aleph Zero Testnet?",
    "response": "This is the raw balance of the address - 50010000000, please adjust for the decimals",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12 00:00:18.803282"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what is the balance of Sam on Polkadot chain?",
    "response": "This is the raw balance of the address - 0, please adjust for the decimals",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12 00:02:17.174492"
  }
]